♬ 立ち上がる勇気を
♬ 惹きあわせる
You bastards!
Don't turn your backs to me!
♬ 受け継ぐ愛を 宿命と呼ぶなら
Take this! Deadly Ripple Bubble Launcher!
♬ 微笑む目で 次の手を
Shijima no soko kara
From out of the stillness
♬ 闇を欺いて
刹那を躱して
♬ 刃すり抜け奴らの間隙を突け
Timing:
Fadeout4
Mezameru sono hashira tachi
The Pillars of the past are awakening
♬ つらぬいた信念が 未来を拓く
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Toki wo koe
To the dawn of a new day
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Shinku no chishio ga
The river of crimson blood within you
♬ Like a Bloody Storm
熱くLike a Bloody Stone
Fadeout4
Typesetting:
♬ 血脈に
刻まれた因縁に
Mazrim
Quality Check:
Tachiagaru yuuki wo hikiawaseru
Carries with it the courage to stand and fight
♬ 浮き上がる消えない誇りの絆
Uketsugu ai wo sadame to yobu nara
Even if the love I feel is just part of my legacy...
♬ 握りしめて
Hohoemu me de tsugi no te wo
I'll still be smiling as I stay one step ahead
Yami wo azamuite setsuna wo kawashite
Defying the darkness and dodging death at every turn
Encoding:
Fadeout4
Yaiba surinuke yatsura no suki wo tsuke
Slipping past the knife's edge and striking when you least expect
Tsuranuita omoi ga mirai wo hiraku
The emotions running through me blaze a path to the future...
Raw Hunter: WRRRRY
Like a bloody storm
Atsuku like a bloody storm
Burning like a bloody storm
Ketsumyaku ni kizamareta innen ni
When the time comes to end the vendetta carried by our blood
Ukiagaru kienai hokori no kizuna
Remember that the bonds of pride will carry you through any storm
Nigirishimete
So hold them close
http://www.some-stuffs.com
Episode 15: "A Hero's Worth"
(ﾜﾑｳ)ぬう！
こ… これは まさか！
I-It couldn't be!
(ｼﾞｮｾﾌ)やった！ いまいましいが
シーザーの波紋は やつに効いた！
Great! Caesar might be a pain, but at least his Ripple works!
貴様は シャボンに囲まれた！
You're surrounded by my bubbles. Now prepare to be bombarded!
続く連弾を 食らえ！
ふぬうっ！
ああっ！
うっ…｡
(ｼｬﾎﾞﾝが割れる音)
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)や… 破れた｡
シャボンランチャーが！
H-He just popped... your Bubble Launcher!
今のは あのワイヤーが
直接 触れて 割ったのではない｡
It wasn't the wires on his head that popped the bubbles...
It was the gust of wind they created!
ワイヤーの起こす風圧が
シャボンを蹴散らしたのだ！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)つまり あのワイヤーは
対波紋のための道具…➡
That means those wires are anti-Ripple weapons!
こいつらは！
波紋の原理を知っているのだ｡➡
WHAM
These monsters already understand how the Ripple works...
...just from when they encountered it two thousand years ago!
こいつらと波紋は！
2,000年前に 出会っている！
AC/DC
CARS
な… 何だ？
こいつらの周りの大気が…｡
W-What's going on with the air surrounding them?
No, Caesar! Get down!
いかん！ シーザー 伏せろ！
What the-?
な… 何だ？
目を閉じろ！ さっきのは
ただの風圧ではない！
Close your eyes! That wasn't just wind, it was the aftermath of a vortex!
小型の真空竜巻の余波だ！
うっ！ うおっ…｡
シーザー！
Caesar!
The Ripple Tribe...
(ｶｰｽﾞ)波紋の一族…｡
I thought we eliminated them all two thousand years ago...
(ｴｼﾃﾞｨｼ)2,000年前に 我らが
全滅させたはずのやつらが➡
このローマの地で 我らの
目覚めるのを待っていたとは…｡
But here they are in Rome, waiting for us to awaken.
ううっ…｡
Damn... you...
なん… の…｡
友人が殺されたのだ！
You killed my friend...
You think losing an eye will stop me?!
目の１つぐらいで
へこたれるか！
フフフフ… フフフフ…｡
き… 貴様ら！ 何がおかしい！
W-What the hell's so funny?!
(ﾜﾑｳ)フフフ… 波紋の一族は
いつも 同じせりふを吐く｡➡
The Ripple Tribe always says the same thing.
It was much like when we crossed over from
the western continent those two thousand years ago.
我々が初めて 西の果ての大陸から
海を越えてきた2,000年前も 今も｡
"You think losing an arm or an eye will stop me?!"
(ﾜﾑｳ)｢腕の１本や 目が
見えぬぐらいで へこたれるか｡➡
よくも友の命を
奪ってくれたな｣と｡➡
"How dare you take my friend's life!"
だから 笑ったのだ｡
This is why we laugh.
き… 貴様ら～！
Y-You monsters!
Let's go. We must locate the Red Stone of Aja.
行くぞ
エイジャの赤石を求めに！
G-Get back here!
ま… 待ちやがれ！
You're running away?!
逃げる気か～！
うっ！ グウァッ…！
Your throat and lungs are your weak points!
貴様らの弱点は 喉か肺だ！
呼吸できなくさせれば 波紋は
使えんということも知っている｡
We know that if you are unable breathe, you cannot use the Ripple.
Now I'll tell you what I always say.
そして俺は
昔も 今も こう言うのだ｡➡
Brat, come and face the mighty Wham
again once you've grown stronger!
｢小僧 今度 会うときは
もっと強くなってから➡
このワムウに向かってこい｣と！
When we meet again, I want to admire your strength...
二度目に お前に会うとき
このワムウが➡
お前の強さを尊敬して
お前を打ち砕き 殺すためにな｡
...before I utterly destroy you.
ぐうっ｡
はぁ… はぁ…｡
It appears there are no other Ripple users.
他に
波紋の仲間は いないようです｡
うむ｡ 行くぞ｡
Let's move.
おほ おほ
おほほん おほ～ん！
おほぉ～ん おほっおほっ｡
ここ！ ここよ ここ！
ここにちゃんと➡
Look over here!
Don't go and ignore me now!
俺がいるのを
見落とさないでほしいのよ～ん｡
フンフン
切れたのは まぶただけだ｡➡
He only scratched your eyelid. It looks like your eyeball is fine.
目ん玉は 大丈夫みてえだぜ｡
Take your cute little Bubble Launcher and hold tight!
何が必殺だよ｡
ｼｬﾎﾞﾝﾗﾝﾁｬｰが敗れちまったお前は
引っ込んどれ！
この俺が きっちりと
片づけてやっからよ｡
I can take care of this.
ジョジョ！
そろそろ 見せてやるぜ！
Jojo!
It's time to show off the brand new technique I've been working on!
考えに考えた➡
俺だけの 出来たてホヤホヤの
必殺技をな！
What?!
何!?
自己紹介させてもらおう｡
Let me introduce myself.
The name's Joseph Joestar, and I'm the guy
who mopped the floor with your buddy.
俺の名は ジョセフ･ジョースター｡
お前らの仲間の１人を
片づけてやった男よ！
I call this the Ripple Clacker Volley!
名付けて
波紋クラッカーヴォレイ！
I start off by filling these American clackers with the Ripple...
このアメリカンクラッカーに
まず 波紋を送り込んでな…｡
あたっ！
Oh no!
オーノー！
ジョジョ！ 何をやっているんだ!?
Jojo, what are you doing?! Now isn't the time to mess around!
こんなときに
ふざけるんじゃあない！
この野郎
俺の友達が死んだというのに！
Why you... My friend was just killed! Yet you act so flippant!
なんてやつだ！
俺は… 俺は大マジだぜ…｡
Me? I'm dead serious.
Caesar, you're still mourning the loss of your friend.
シーザーは
友人が殺され 怒り悲しむ｡
I can feel your pain and anger.
それもある｡ それは怒る｡
But more than that, I can't stand egotistical jerks like these guys!
だがな… 俺はもともと➡
こういう傲慢な野郎が
どうしても許せねえタチなんだ！
I'm not an expert yet, but let's see what you think of my Clacker Volley!
練習不足だが 見てろ！
この俺の必殺
クラッカーヴォレイの妙技を！
ぬ？
俺の波紋は➡
I hate to admit it, but my the Ripple is still weak.
悔しいが 確かに まだ弱いぜ…｡
だがな！ この
鋼鉄のクラッカーヴォレイで➡
But on the other hand, I can use my Clacker Volley
to cut into your skin and hit you with the Ripple.
てめえの皮膚を砕いてから
そこへ 波紋を流し込めばよ➡
That should even out my handicap.
それで 俺の弱点は
カバーされんのよ！
Pretty good, right?
どうだ！ すげえだろ！
Take this!
食らえ！
ぐっ…｡
(ｴｼﾃﾞｨｼ)フフフッ もう行くぞ｡
Let's go.
(ｶｰｽﾞ)
フッ あきれる｡ 人間は 昔に比べ
退化したのかもしれんな｡
How absurd.
Perhaps humans have regressed over the years.
Regressed?
退化ですと？
フフッ 確かに！
Perhaps so.
くっ…！
ジョジョ！ ふざけやがって！
Jojo, quit playing around!
All you did was throw metal spheres at them!
ただ 鉄の玉を
投げただけじゃあねえか！
Jojo... Jojo really isn't taking this seriously!
He's acting like this is just some normal thug!
《ジョジョは…
ジョジョは 本当は➡
真面目に 戦おうと
しているのかもしれない｡➡
街のゴロツキ相手ならいい｡➡
But... these beings surpass him in every way!
しかし こいつらに対しては
完全に 浮いてしまっている！➡
Seeing him so outmatched is devastating!
悲しいほど 滑稽に見える！》
Crap! Nobody here is taking me seriously!
くそっ どいつもこいつも
俺をバカにしやがって！
Hold it, big guy! You're gonna get hit!
おいこら 待ちな 兄ちゃん！
後ろから どつくぞ！
Don't.
(ﾜﾑｳ)やめろ！
人間の寿命は どうせ短い｡
Human lives are short enough. Do not rush to die.
死に急ぐ必要もなかろう｡
Shut it! Spaghetti nero looks bad too, but it's a real treat!
ちくしょう！ ｽﾊﾟｹﾞｯﾃｨﾈｰﾛだって
見てくれは悪いが 味は最高よ！
You need to have a taste of my Clacker Volley before you judge it!
クラッカーヴォレイの真の妙味を
味わってから ほざいてもらおう！
(ｼｰｻﾞｰ･ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)あっ！
The clackers vanished!
クラッカーの鋼鉄球が消えた！
I've been working on the railroad, all the live-long day!
せえ～んろは つづく～よ｡
どぉ～こまぁでもぉ～！
L-Look!
あ… あれは!?
ん？
ヘヘ かかったな｡
まだ分かんない？
How's that? Are you still fooled?
フヘヘヘヘ 分かってないなら…｡
If you don't get it...
...let me show you!
見せてやるぜ！ 食らえ てめえ！
Take this, fella!
うっ！
げっ！
Those moves are impossible!
なんという不可能な姿勢！
He's moving even faster than Santana!
しかも その変形のスピードは
サンタナ以上だ！
The clackers didn't even touch him!
クラッカーは かすりもせずに
ふっ飛んでいく始末！
(ﾜﾑｳ)フフフハハ
お前の その武器と➡
I admire your weapon, your courage, and you tactics.
度胸とアイデアに 敬意を表そう｡
Things are becoming interesting.
面白くなってきた｡ だから１分…｡
Thus...
I'll give you one minute.
１分だ｡ １分だけ お前に
このワムウと戦う時間をやろう｡
I bestow upon you a single minute to fight the mighty Wham.
うわ～！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ジョジョ！
Jojo!
As you can see, I've slit your wrist right down to the artery.
(ﾜﾑｳ)
見てのとおり 手首を切った！
傷は 動脈まで達している｡➡
In other words, you have one minute to tend to that wound
before you lose consciousness from blood loss.
つまり
１分以内に止血しなければ➡
お前は 出血多量で
失神するというわけだ｡
Give me everything you've got!
(ﾜﾑｳ)
必死になって かかって来い！
うお…｡
This is what I have always said to members of the Ripple Tribe:
昔も 今も
俺は 波紋の一族にこう言う｡
"Here is an hourglass measured in blood."
｢砂時計ならぬ 戦いの血時計｣よ｡
Wham, we'll be waiting outside.
ワムウ 外で待っているぞ｡
小僧 飛ばされた武器を
拾いに行けィ｡
Boy, go pick up your weapon!
Huh? What? What'd you just say?
え？ 何？
今 何て言ったんだ？
"Go pick up your weapon?" Is that what you said?
拾いに行け？
拾いに行けだって～？
That won't be necessary!
その必要はない！
拾いに行く必要は 全然ねえのよ！
I have no need to go pick it up.
む？
ぐうっ！
ああっ！
That was my Clacker Boomerang!
名付けて クラッカーブーメラン！
１分とは お前の命の方だったな！
One minute is all I need to beat you!
おあっ！
Make fun of me, will you? I'll smash you to pieces!
人をバカにした てめえの態度を
文字通り 打ち砕いてやるぜ！
Then I'll finish you with the Ripple!
波紋を傷口に流すのは
それからだ！
Very well.
(ﾜﾑｳ)よかろう｡ もっと打て！
これまで このワムウの顔に➡
Hit me all you like.
You are the first person to scar my face.
傷を付けた者は
いないのだから｡➡
And for that reason, I will bestow this honor upon you before you die...
それが お前にこのワムウが授ける
死の前の名誉｡
You're telling me no one has ever hit your face before?
今まで 自分の顔を殴った人間は
いないだと？
Big words!
よく言うぜ！
You didn't even bat an eye when you killed Mark!
マルクを残忍に殺しても
気付きもしねえ｡
その お高くとまった態度
後悔させてやる！
I'll make you regret holding your nose so high!
Look out! He's up to something!
I don't think you're hurting him anymore!
いかん！ 何か出る！
あの腕 ダメージを受けているとは
とても思えん！
うっ!?
Th-This is gonna be bad!
な… 何か ヤバい雰囲気｡
You have good instincts to jump back.
飛びのいたのは いい勘だ｡
I let you hit me to punish myself for getting caught off guard.
あえて お前に殴らせたのは➡
油断した自分を 戒めるためであり
その教訓とするため｡
But that has ended.
だが それも終わりだ｡
Jojo, hurry and finish him!
ジョジョ！
早く とどめを刺すんだ！
Here is my technique.
(ﾜﾑｳ)闘技 神砂嵐！
Holy Sandstorm!
I-I'm in trouble!
こ… これは まずい！
He spins his left arm clockwise!
(ﾅﾚｰｼｮﾝ)
〈左腕を 関節ごと右回転！
右腕を 関節ごと左回転！➡
And his right arm counter-clockwise!
Jojo is caught unaware, and Wham's fists seem to grow before his eyes!
結構 のんきしてたジョジョも➡
拳が一瞬
巨大に見えるほどの➡
回転圧力には ビビッた！〉
うぉぉぉぉぉああああああああ！
〈その２つの拳の間に生じる
真空状態の圧倒的破壊空間は➡
The space between his fists becomes a destructive vacuum!
まさに 歯車的砂嵐の小宇宙！〉
The whirling creates a torrent of wind and sand!
だ… 大理石の柱がっ！
こ… こんな不自然な形に｡
He ripped through that marble pillar like a piece of old cloth!
雑巾みてえに！ 異常だ！
この破壊力…｡
I've never seen such power!
おおおおおお！
ジョジョ…｡
Jojo...
That was my Holy Sandstorm.
(ﾜﾑｳ)これが 神砂嵐｡
Jo... Jojo!
ジョ… ジョジョ～！
だ… 駄目だ！ 行っては！
N-No, stay back!
Mr. Speedwagon, you have to get out of here!
スピードワゴンさん
あなただけ 逃げてください！
I'll do something to hold him back!
せめて ここは
俺が 何とか食い止める！
(ﾜﾑｳ)
目に血が入り 方向を誤ったが➡
The blood in my eye threw off my aim...
...but it was enough, even when you hid behind the pillar.
柱の陰ぐらいに逃れても
ダメージは十分よ｡
くたばったか｡➡
Dead already?
そして ただの人間どもなど
どうでもよいのだが➡
Ordinarily, I would ignore humans like yourselves.
このワムウの
屈辱の姿を見られたからには➡
But you witnessed my shame, so I must be rid of you as well.
貴様らも
始末せねばならなくなった！
Prepare yourselves!
覚悟してもらうぞ｡
あっ！
ん？
ふむ 気のせいか｡
I'm imagining things.
はぁ… はぁ…｡
H-He couldn't be!
《あ… あいつ まさか!?➡
U-Unbelievable. He's trying to escape!
な… なんて男だ｡
逃げようとしている！》
ヌウ？
ふん…｡
Playing dead like that... He has no shame!
《死んだふりまでして
見損なったぜ！➡
俺はともかく ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝさんまで
ほっぽり出すとは！➡
I can understand leaving me, but Mr. Speedwagon? How spineless!
やつは クズだった！》
That guy is the biggest menace I've seen!
《すさまじい…
ヤバい相手だぜ｡➡
俺は もう
呼吸は乱れちまってるから➡
My breathing is out of control. I can't use the Ripple!
波紋は使えない｡➡
残るは 俺の十八番の策…➡
I only have my specialty left...
逃げるだけしかできない！》
All I can do is run!
Look at our dismal hero!
〈見よ！
この無様な ヒーローの姿を！➡
Jojo is on the ground, forced to play dead.
ジョジョは 地面をなめながら
死んだふりまでして➡
しかも スピードワゴンを
置いてまで 逃げ出している！➡
He's about to leave Speedwagon to his fate!
Even so, Jojo will still remain the worthy hero of this tale!
だが！
だからといって ジョジョが➡
この物語の ヒーローの資格を
失いはしない！➡
なぜなら！〉
Here's why!
くっ… うう…
はぁ… はぁ…｡
(ﾜﾑｳ)
ヌウウ！ 貴様 生きているな！
Still alive, are you?!
You coward!
(ﾜﾑｳ)ひきょう者め！
このワムウをだまして➡
You thought you could trick me and escape?!
逃げおおせるとでも思ったか！
ヌウ!?
ヘヘヘヘッ あんたをだますのは
ほんの 十数ｍでよかったのよ｡
I only needed to fool you for a few dozen yards.
All I needed was to get to this mine cart.
つまり トロッコまでたどりつけば
ＯＫだったのね｡
So you only acted like a coward to
lure me over and let your friends escape, eh?
そうか お前
２人を逃がすために➡
ひきょう者のまねまでして
逆に 俺を誘ったな!?
And you fell for another one of my tricks.
あんた また俺の策に
はまっちゃったわけね｡
Old man, get out of here, now!
《じいさん
この隙に 逃げてくれ！➡
Caesar, you too!
シーザー ついでに お前もな！》
ジョジョ…｡
あの野郎 味なことを！
Jojo...
That bastard... has some nerve!
I've sure painted myself into a corner...
《とは言っても 俺も絶体絶命！➡
I need to come up with something.
また何か
策を考えなくっちゃあな…➡
What a pain...
やれやれ》
フフフフッ｡
〈紛れもない ヒーロー！➡
An unbending hero!
Only if Jojo lost his will to fight would he lose his status as a hero.
ヒーローの資格を 失うとすれば➡
戦う意志を ジョジョが
なくしたときだけなのだ！〉
Jojo!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ジョジョ～‼
Dammit! He's far more injured than I am!
ちくしょう！
俺の傷より 重傷のくせして！
《ジョジョは ふざけた態度こそ
取ってはいるが➡
He may put on a foolish act, but he takes his fate seriously.
やつは やつなりに
自分の宿命を真剣に考えている｡➡
あの怪物どもを 倒さなくては
ならないという 宿命を！》
He knows he has to beat those monsters!
はぁ… はぁ…｡
You speak quite brashly for one in such a terrible state.
そこまで ズタボロになりながら
今なお 不敵なまなざしを持ち➡
生意気なせりふを吐く！➡
You're a tough man.
タフな男よ！
ちっぽけな根性が 実にタフだ！
Weak-spirited, but tough indeed.
How are you so tough?
なぜ そんなにタフだ？
脳みそが くそになってるのか？
Is your brain defective, or do you have another trick for me?
それとも このワムウと
渡り合う策が 他にあるのか？
You want to know?
聞きたいのか？
まさか その策とは…｡
Don't tell me...
Is it something stupid like going into
the mine and using explosives on me?
あの発掘現場から
抜け目なく くすねておいた➡
そのチンケな物を
爆発させようという➡
くだらないアイデアか？
Crap! He knows!
《ヤベえ！ 読まれた！》
Or do you plan to pull the brake and send the mine cart flying?
それともまさか！ このトロッコを
急ブレーキをかけて➡
転覆させよう
というのではあるまいな？
Something like this?
こんなふうに！
うわぁぁ！
《ま… また読まれた！》
H-He did it again!
(ｶｰｽﾞ･ｴｼﾃﾞｨｼ)ヌッ！
(ﾜﾑｳ)手首の血時計は
じき 時間切れとなる…｡
The time on your wristwatch is almost up.
There is zero percent chance you'll survive this.
貴様の命が助かる可能性は０％だ｡
You are out of tricks.
(ﾜﾑｳ)貴様には もう策はない…｡
ふん…｡
But tell me this...
だのに なぜだ？
その不敵なまなざしの理由は？
Why don't I see defeat in your eyes?
聞きたいのか？ 本当に聞きたい？
You want to know?
You really want to know?
(ﾜﾑｳ)いや！ 聞かんでもいい！
やはり すぐ殺すことにした！
No, it doesn't matter. I'll just kill you now.
If you give me a month, I'll become strong enough to beat you.
１か月ありゃあ
俺は お前なんか倒すほど➡
強くなってみせるのになあ｡
What was that?
(ﾜﾑｳ)何だと？
１か月あれば➡
Give me a month and I'll surpass you.
お前より強くなると言ったんだ｡
I'm the first person to scar your face.
俺は お前の額に
初めて 傷を付けた男だぜ｡
ちょいと努力すれば
簡単に強くなれるのさ｡
If I put my mind to it, my potential is limitless.
No, never mind what I said.
いや… 今 言ったこと
忘れちまってくれ！
さっ 早いとこ とどめを刺せよ｡
Well, finish me off quickly.
こんな立派で 強い戦士に
殺されるんだ｡ 名誉なことだぜ！
It's an honor to be killed by a warrior like you.
話を続けろ！
Continue.
Oh, I'm tired of talking!
あ～ しゃべるのも
だるくなってきた｡
Make it painless, Wham.
せめて 楽に殺してくれ ワムウ｡
続けろ！ と言っているのだ！
I told you to continue!
あっ…｡
Jojo is still okay!
ジョジョのやつ まだ無事だ…｡
You have a long life ahead of you.
いやね… あんたは
これからの長～い人生を➡
You'll have to carry the shame of being scarred by a human.
ただの人間に 額を傷つけられた
汚点を背負って➡
生きていくわけだ｡
The only way to fix that is by beating me
in a fair fight after I've trained.
それを拭うのは
強く鍛え抜かれて 成長した俺と➡
正式に戦って
勝つことだと思うのだよ｡
What? Don't feed me your lies, Jojo!
何!? ハッタリをかますなよ
ジョジョとやら！
I only need a bit more to get to him!
《もう少しで 完璧に釣れるぜ！➡
こいつ 俺が逃げ出したとき
｢ひきょう者｣と叫んだ！➡
He called me a coward when I ran...
Using a word like that means he's the "proud warrior" type.
ひきょう者というせりふ！➡
つまり 戦いに
誇りを重んずるタイプと見たぜ｡➡
その心理を突いてやる！》
I can use that against him!
I'm a bit new to fighting.
今の俺は
戦いの素人なんだぜ！
波紋の修行を 正式に積めば➡
But if I train with the Ripple for a month,
I know I have the talent to beat you!
たったの１か月で
貴様より強くなる才能がある！
何しろ ５cmも
その額をえぐったのは➡
I was the first human to hit your head,
and I was able to carve a chunk out of it!
歴史上！ ただのカスみてえな
この俺なんだからなあ！
でも もっとも
この俺が 強くならないうちに➡
But you still have a chance to kill me
before I grow into a real threat to you!
殺してしまった方が
あんたにとって いいよね｡
ぐぐっ…｡
Why you-!
貴様～！
(ｴｼﾃﾞｨｼ)ワムウ！
Wham.
(ﾜﾑｳ)エシディシ様！
Master AC/DC.
もう １分過ぎたぞ｡
His minute is up. Why do you allow him to live?
なぜ そいつを
さっさと始末しない？ おっ？
《うぅ… ヤバい｡ 仲間だ》
Crap, it's his friend!
うぐ…｡
ん？
うおお…！
Master AC/DC, I've grown fond of this wielder of the Ripple.
エシディシ様｡
私は この波紋使いを➡
えらく 気に入りました｡
I-I got him!
《き… きた！》
Jojo, is it?
ジョジョとやら！ 俺はあえて
お前の口車に 乗ってやるぞ！
I agree to your proposition!
いいだろう！
１か月で強くなると言うのなら➡
You say you will be stronger in a month,
so I will give you a month to live.
１か月だけ
命をくれてやろうではないか！
俺を殺さねえの？
そうだ｡
You aren't gonna kill me?
Indeed.
We'll fight again?
俺と再試合？
そうだ｡
Indeed!
This is a bad idea. You'll regret it.
やめとけよ｡
今 殺さないと 後悔するぜ｡
Yes! I'm safe for now!
《おお やったぞ！
ひとまず 助かるぜ！》
However...
(ﾜﾑｳ)ただし お前が
逃げたままでおれんように➡
I need to ensure that you will not simply run away.
儀式を施す！
Wham, will you be using that old thing again?
ははん！ ワムウ
いつものやつをやるというわけか｡
The Wedding Ring of Death.
(ﾜﾑｳ)名付けて
死のウエディングリング！➡
I will put this ring around your aorta.
今から このリングを
心臓の動脈に引っ掛けておく｡
W-What are you doing?!
な… 何をする!?
(ﾜﾑｳ)このリングの外殻は
33日後に溶け始める｡➡
The ring will start to dissolve in thirty-three days.
Inside is a virulent poison.
リングの中には
毒薬が入っている｡➡
The ring cannot be removed. Any attempt
will break it, releasing the poison!
手術で取り出すことはできない！
無理に取り出そうとすれば➡
殻はあっという間に破れ
毒は流れ出す｡
うわ～！
You have only one way to avoid the poison...
(ﾜﾑｳ)毒が体内に回らんうちに
助かる方法は ただ１つ！
33日以内に 俺と戦って勝ち➡
Fight and defeat me within thirty-three days
and take the antidote from my lip piercing!
俺の このピアスの中にある
解毒剤を飲むことのみ！
ジョジョ！
Jojo!
"Till death do us part," a true wedding ring.
まさに 死が２人を分かつまでの
ウエディングリングよ！
33日後の真夜中！
Midnight in thirty-three days at the Colosseum
is where I will wait for you, Jojo.
このローマのコロッセオで
待っているぞ ジョジョ！
フフ このまま 逃げ出すつもりで
いたのだろうが 当てが外れたな｡
You guessed wrong if you thought you could escape.
I don't imagine we'll fight, but here's a little present from AC/DC!
俺との戦いは ないだろうが➡
このエシディシからも
プレゼントだ！
ゲーッ！
I'll put it around your windpipe!
(ｴｼﾃﾞｨｼ)貴様の喉に
埋め込ませてもらうぞ！
うわ～っ！ 心臓と喉！
My heart and throat!
Mine is a different poison from Wham's.
The antidote is in my nose piercing.
ワムウとは違う毒よ！
俺の解毒剤は
この鼻のピアスにある｡
Cars, you want in?
カーズ お前も埋め込むか？
Nonsense.
くだらぬ｡
もっとも 我々は不老不死｡
We are immortal.
A worthy opponent is a rare thing that gives our lives meaning.
好敵手がいなくて 久しい｡
敵があってこそ 張りのある人生｡
気持ちは 分からんでもないがな｡
I can understand why you're doing it...
...but our main goal is to obtain the power of the Red Stone of Aja.
だが 我らの第一目的は➡
エイジャの赤石のパワーを
手に入れること｡
忘れるなよ ２人とも｡ 行くぞ！
Do not forget that, you two.
Let's go!
(ﾜﾑｳ)ジョジョ！
せいぜい強くなり➡
Jojo, grow strong and overcome my Holy Sandstorm!
俺の神砂嵐を破ってみろ！
(ｴｼﾃﾞｨｼ)フハハハハハハ！
はぁ… はぁ…｡
な… なんてこった…｡
W-What the hell?
A wedding ring? That's some black humor if I've ever heard it!
ウエディングリングだと？
とんだ ブラックユーモアだぜ｡
ちくしょう！
ご丁寧に ２個も埋めやがって…｡
And now I've got two of them!
Do I look like a damn polygamist or something?!
２個じゃあ 重婚罪じゃねえか！
くそったれ！
ぐはぁ…｡
《まあ でも スピードワゴンも
シーザーも助かったし➡
Well, at least Speedwagon and Caesar are safe.
くよくよ考えても
しょうがねえか…》
There's no sense in getting down about it.
あっ…｡
ジョジョ 貴様…｡
Jojo.
You damned fool...
《出血多量で
意識もうろうでありながら➡
Despite the blood you lost, you pulled a first-rate bluff
that would impress even the best gambler!
一流の賭博師さながらの
心理戦のブラッフ 見事だった！➡
How amazing!
波紋の修行につきあうぜ！➡
Let's study the Ripple together.
強く成長するんだ｡
俺も お前もな》
We'll grow stronger...
You and me both.
In and around the lake
♬ In and around the lake
♬ Mountains come out of
the sky and they stand there
Mountains come out of the sky
They stand there
♬ Twenty four before
my love I'll be there
Twenty four before my love and I'll be there
♬～
Next Episode
I only said one month as a bluff!
Step through those doors and you'll see!
Master, you can't!
I won't hold back because you're a girl!
Welcome to Venice!
Episode 16:
"Lisa Lisa, Master of the Ripple"
ハッタリのつもりで
１か月って言ったのによ！
(ﾘｻﾘｻ)この塔の中に落ちれば
よく分かる｡
先生！ まさか！
俺は 女だろうが容赦はしねえ！
ようこそ ヴェネチアへ｡